<?xml version="1.0"?>
<LocalizationData xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <items>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>intro0</key>
      <value>Pangram, the letter volcano, is about to erupt!

Legend tells of a magical prodigy whose mastery of words and strategy will save the day.  Spell words by selecting adjacent tiles in any of the 8 directions.  For instance, following the yellow arrows to spell GUITAR in the example below.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>intro1</key>
      <value>Longer words improve your fortune, which means better replacement letters.  Oh, but the jumble of letters, what is a Wizard to do?  

You will advance your magical skills through levels, and when they are high enough, you will gain magic spells that are added to your book.  Casting these spells require mana, which you collect by spelling words with purple mana tiles.  

You are also awarded free spells, earned by spelling long or high scoring words.  They do not require any mana to cast.

Spell higher scoring and longer words by strategically rearranging the letter tiles using the spells you have available, and any that have been awarded.

But beware of lava, the RED letter tile in the above example, because if they reach the bottom the game is over.  Keep the lava tiles away and earn the highest score.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>HelpButton</key>
      <value>Help</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>HighScore</key>
      <value>High Scores</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>BestWords</key>
      <value>Best Words</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>LongestWords</key>
      <value>Longest</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>BestOverallWords</key>
      <value>Best Words including bonuses</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Start9x9</key>
      <value>Start 9x9</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Start7x7</key>
      <value>Start 7x7</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Level</key>
      <value>Level</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Score</key>
      <value>Score</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Mana</key>
      <value>Mana</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Fortune</key>
      <value>Fortune</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Spells</key>
      <value>Spells</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Audition</key>
      <value>Audition</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Free</key>
      <value>free</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Close</key>
      <value>Close</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Quit</key>
      <value>Quit</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Email</key>
      <value>Email</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Yes</key>
      <value>Yes</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>No</key>
      <value>No</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>OK</key>
      <value>OK</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>NewSpell</key>
      <value>You have new spells.  Spells require Mana which you collect by spelling words using purple Mana tiles.
	  
	  
	  </value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>NoWordSpelledMsg</key>
      <value>Select adjacent tiles in any direction to spells words.  When the word is valid, submit button will turn green.  Words must be 3 or more letters long.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>LessThanThreeMsg</key>
      <value>Only words greater than 3 letters are accepted.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>NewLevel</key>
      <value>Welcome to Level </value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>NiceWord</key>
      <value>Nice word, you've earned a </value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>BestWordIs</key>
      <value>Your best word is </value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>LongestWordIs</key>
      <value>Your Longest word is </value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Spell</key>
      <value>spell</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Stuck</key>
      <value>You seem stuck, do you want to me to find you a word?</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>UsedAlready</key>
      <value>You've used that word already.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>NeedVowels</key>
      <value>You seem to be low on vowels.  To help you out, we've granted you a vowel dust spell.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>SubmitButtonDefault</key>
      <value>Click on letters 
to spell a word</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>SubmitButtonAlreadyUsed</key>
      <value> already used.
</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>SubmitButtonSubmit</key>
      <value>, submit?
</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>IncorrectWordPhrases</key>
      <value>Nice word...if you are a Martian :)  Please try again.
Good try, but only earthbound languages will work.
I'm sure you think that's a word, but it's not in my dictionary
Creative, but that's not a word.
Not every combination of letters spell a word.
Do you need your reading glass, because that's not a word.
You sure do have a knack for spelling gibberish.
I'm not sure gibberish is a language.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>NextLevelMsg</key>
      <value>Level 2 introduces light blue tiles which doubles the letter value
Beware of lava tiles, if they reach the bottom, the game is over
Level 4 introduces pink word tiles which doubles the word score
Level 5 introduces darker blue letter tiles which triples the letter value
Level 6 introduces darker pink word tiles which triples the word score</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>EndGameReasons</key>
      <value>You've ended the game, please play again.
The lava has reached the bottom, the city is doomed.  Please try again.
There are no more words for you to spell, please try again.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>HintPhrase</key>
      <value>There are a lot of words in here, how about </value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>HintNotFound</key>
      <value>Uh oh, there are no words left, do you have any spells that could help?</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>MagicCancel</key>
      <value>Cancel</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Snipe</key>
      <value>Select one letter to destroy, then press the wand button.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Swap</key>
      <value>Pick two adjacent tile up/down/left/right, the press the wand button.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Burn</key>
      <value>Select a single tile to become lava, then press the wand button.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>VowelDust</key>
      <value>Press the wand button to sprinkle vowels randomly on the grid.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>ConvertLetter</key>
      <value>Chose a letter to convert, then press the wand and all letters of that kind will be randomized.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Bomb</key>
      <value>Pick a tile to destroy it and it's up/down/left/right neighbors, then press the wand button.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>CWRotate</key>
      <value>Pick a tile and then press the wand button to rotate the surrounding tiles clockwise once.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>CCWRotate</key>
      <value>Pick a tile and then press the wand button to rotate the surrounding tiles counter-clockwise once.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Hint</key>
      <value>Press the wand button to provide a decent hint, if one exists.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Rotate180</key>
      <value>Pick a tile and then press the wand button to rotate the surrounding tiles 180 degrees.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>HintPlus</key>
      <value>Press the wand button to provide the best word possible, if one exists.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Vowelize</key>
      <value>Pick one letter to change into a random vowel, then press the wand button.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>HintLet</key>
      <value>Pick a letter, the press the wand button, and we'll try to find a hint that uses that letter.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>AnyLetter</key>
      <value>Pick a letter to change.  After pressing the wand, you can enter the letter of your choice.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>RowGone</key>
      <value>Select a row, then the wand button to make it gone.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>ColGone</key>
      <value>Select a column, then the wand button to make it gone.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>Blackout</key>
      <value>Press the wand button and the entire grid will be replaced with new letters.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>AnyLetterDefault</key>
      <value>type a letter?</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>NewMusic</key>
      <value>The background music hasn't changed in a while.  If you use the speaker in a word, the music will change as a new speaker is created.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
    <LocalizationItem>
      <key>NewMusicSnipe</key>
      <value>The background music hasn't changed in a while.  You've been given a Snipe spell to remedy that situation if you wish.</value>
    </LocalizationItem>
  </items>
</LocalizationData>